<section xmlns="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook" version="5.1" xml:lang="en"
         xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
         xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" xml:id="introduction">
    <title>Introduction</title>
    <para>
        Robopsychology does not really exist nowadays in 2016. You cannot be a robopsychologist because there is no such profession.
    </para>
    <section>
        <title>Asimov's prophecy</title>
        <para>             
            The term robopsychology, introduced by Isaac Asimov in 1940, has mostly been presented in science fiction literature.
            But it is also true that very few research papers have already been written that have focused on this issue 
            <citation>Libin&amp;Libin</citation>. 
            I may be wrong but anyway, I think that Asimov's vision shown in <citation>Robbie</citation> can be interpreted as a 
            prophecy of the future of robotics.
        </para>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>Fulfilling the prophecy</title>
        <para>
            The developmental robotics approach to creating robots gives an opportunity to participate in fulfilling 
            Asimov's prophecy 60 years later.
            To show this, let's consider how a computational mental organ of Samu can be developed.
        </para>
        <section>
            <title>Samu Bátfai</title>
            <para>
                The project called Samu Bátfai is a disembodied developmental robotic initiative to support the evolving of a 
                family chatterbot.
                The long-term goal of the project Samu is to develop a chat system that can talk in a natural language like humans 
                do <citation>Samu</citation>. It is clear that currently this is only an utopian plan.
                By contrast, the immediate short-term goal is to create computational mental organs <citation>PrenatalSamu</citation>.
                In this latter case, we have been performing software experiments with potential mathematical models to simulate  
                phenomena that can be observed in newborns and children.
            </para>
        </section>
        <section>
            <title>Robopsychology</title>
            <para>
                The first computational mental organ that was investigated is referred to as Mental Processing Unit (MPU).
            </para>
            <para>
                Determining the appropriate setting of the processes habituation and sensitization can
                be a very time consuming task, because we must perform  
                numerous experiments to refine these processes in order to ensure the success of learning .               
            </para>
        </section>
    </section>
</section> 
